/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data9_1', {
    title: '9.1 Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
    path: '9.1-add-and-subtract-like-fractions  ',
    children: [{ //----1
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{4}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----2
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{8}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{2}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----3
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{9}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{9}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{8}}{\\input{9}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{9}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{9}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{9}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----4
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{25}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{25}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{24}}{\\input{25}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{25}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{25}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{24}}{\\str{25}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----5
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{6}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{6}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{6}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----6
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{13}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{13}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{8}}{\\input{13}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{13}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{13}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{13}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----7
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{28}}{\\str{42}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{42}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{19}}{\\input{42}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{28}}{\\str{42}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{42}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{19}}{\\str{42}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----8
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{40}}{\\str{66}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{66}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{25}}{\\input{66}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{40}}{\\str{66}}}{\\sign{-}}{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{66}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{25}}{\\str{66}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----9
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{30}}{\\str{49}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{30}}{\\str{49}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\mixed{\\input{1}}{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{49}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{30}}{\\str{49}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{30}}{\\str{49}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\mixed{\\str{1}}{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{49}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----10
        title: 'Add and Subtract Like Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{30}}{\\str{77}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{35}}{\\str{77}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\input{65}}{\\input{77}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\str{30}}{\\str{77}}}{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\str{35}}{\\str{77}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{65}}{\\str{77}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, ]
});
